[Music]
George's birthday today is George's
birthday it is very early in the morning
it sounds like someone's up bright and
early happy birthday George George woke
me up you woke everyone up on your
birthday Pablo that was different that
was my birthday and today is George's
birthday here's your present George
[Music]
squeeze its tummy George I've made you a
birthday card can you guess what the
picture is George cannot guess I was
going to paint you a flower Oh George
does not like flowers but in the end I
painted you that's a lovely picture
Peppa
yes I'm very good at painting now we're
going somewhere very special for
George's birthday treat
[Applause]
where are we going you see the family
are sitting on the George's Berkeley
treated somewhere just as good where can
they be going here the family have
arrived at the Museum come on you'll see
what can George's birthday treat be
George what do you like best in the
whole world George's birthday treat is a
visit to the museum dinosaur room George
it's not a real dinosaur it's just a
robot
look I stand on this spot and now
there's another surprise Peppa's friends
mummy rabbit has made a birthday cake
for George can anyone guess what sort of
cake it is a dinosaur cake this is
what's an amazing guest Peppa there's
one last surprise follow thee
what is the last surprise what do you
think it is pepper it's probably
something to do with dinosaurs
oh what's that it just needs to be
filled with their bouncy castles George
why isn't it something to do with
dinosaurs it is a dinosaur a bouncy
dinosaur Suzy sheep has come to play at
Peppa's house it's a photograph not a
baby
it's an old photo when I was a baby
don't be silly Suzy in the olden days
you were a baby - Peppa no I wasn't yes
you were ask your mummy mummy pig is
working on the computer no I'm not I was
a baby well you were pepper look here
are some photos on the computer who do
you think that is it's baby Alexander
baby Alexander is Peppa's cousin no
that's you as a baby pepper
somebody sounds like they're having fun
I remember it well it was taken on our
first day in this house what do you mean
when you were little we moved into this
house we brought all our things on top
of our car
mummy pig put some pictures up daddy pig
put up a shelf and grandpa pig made us a
lovely flower garden daddy pig looked
after it we had the wrong kind of soil
for flowers
anyway you needed somewhere to play you
and Suzy loved to play in the garden my
friend in olden days yes you and Suzy
have always been best friends
[Music]
no pepper you were babies you couldn't
even walk soon after that you were
toddlers he was a baby in my tummy yes
you were in my tummy George no pepper
this tummy is pure muscle
and so George was born and granny and
Grandpa gave George a very special
present can you guess what it was that's
right and you and Suzy were running and
jumping around then one day you saw
something amazing pepper if you jump in
muddy puddles you must wear your boots
you loved jumping up and down in muddy
puddles let's take a photo now always
jumping up and down in muddy puddles
[Music]
George is playing with his favorite toy
mr. dinosaur George loves playing with
mr. dinosaur mr. dinosaur is made of
plastic it is almost impossible to break
him George loves playing with mr.
dinosaur in the bath at nighttime George
always takes mr. dinosaur to bed with
him mr. dinosaur does not have a tail
anymore poor George
do you have had mr. dinosaur a long time
I'm surprised he lasted as long as he
did maybe it's about time you got a new
day
- all yes we can go to mr. Fox's shop
tomorrow
this is mr. Fox's shop mr. Fox's shop
sells everything I'm sure we'll find you
a lovely new dinosaur here George George
does not want a new dinosaur
look George a big dinosaur good morning
can I help you
we'd like the dinosaur in the window
please certainly good choice this is the
Dino roar roars it walks and it sings a
dinosaur song Dino lure Dino roar Flitz
included idol war we'll take it
George is playing with Dino roar in the
garden don't play too roughly with Dino
roar George he has moving parts and
might get broken George cannot play with
Dino roar in the garden George wants to
play with Dino roar in the bath
George if you get Dino roar wet he'll
stop working George cannot play with
Dino roar in the bath
it is nighttime George has taken Dinah
raw to bed with him maybe Daniel or
should sleep somewhere else George
cannot have diner raw in his bed at
night it is morning
why is George looking so sad George
cannot play with Dino roar in the garden
in the bath or in bed never mind George
Dino roar can still raw oh I think the
batteries must have run out daddy pig
already Dino roar needs lots of
batteries to make him roar that's not a
trumpet pepper you found mr. dinosaur's
tail
oh now daddy pig can mend him I'll try
hmmm I think it might be quite difficult
to mend
Oh daddy pig has mended mr. dinosaur oh
I am a bit of an expert at mending
things George loves mr. dinosaur
hello mr. dinosaur mr. dinosaur is
George's favorite toy in the whole world
[Music]